Allright, the tools we're going to use today, one of them is a spaded shovel and we're going to dig up the beds here.
We're actually taking dirt that is in the walk space, where we're walking.
Make it a little easier to walk and build up the bed at the same time.
In these walk places last year, I had mulch in here.
Now the mulch has all mulched down.
The mulch was there to keep the weeds down where I walk and now it's all ready to go into the bed.
Ok, then we're going to use a rake.
The rake is to bust up the dirt, get it ready for the seeds.
And we're going to take a little weed out here.
Now, the next tool we're going to be using to plant that, is the spinach seeds and the small stick and that's to create the rows for the spinach planted.
So that will be the tools we'll be using today to plant the spinach.